Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Labor Movement Serials WAG.345
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Labor Research, 1915-2008; 5.75 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 5 oversize flat boxes
  - Society for the study of Labour History Bulletin: Society for the study of Labour History, 1960-1969, 1987-1989 (Box 162, Folder 1-4)
  - General Strike France 1968: A Factory-by-Factory Account: Sojourner Truth Organization, Chicago, IL, circa 1970s (Box 161, Folder 48)
  - 36 Years - Drawings: The Worker, 1960 (Box 172, Folder 51)
  - Let's Have the Truth: Thompson, Cleveland, OH, 1944 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - International Runaway Shop: Why US Companies Are Moving Their Plants Abroad: United Front Press, San Francisco, CA, 1972 (Box 161, Folder 49)
  - Bulletin No. 1026 - Elements of Soviet Labor Law: United States Department of Labor, 1951 (Box 161, Folder 50)
  - Labor Research Center News and Notes: University of Rhode Island, Kingston, RI, 1997, 2006 (Box 161, Folder 51)
  - Letters to Judd: An American Workingman: Upton Sinclair, Pasadena, CA, 1932 (Box 161, Folder 52)
  - Labor Press Service: US Department of Labor, Washington, DC, 1956 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Phillips-Van Heusen Campaign Update: US/Guatemala Labor Education Project, Chicago, IL, 1992 (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - US/Labor Education in the Americas Project: US/Labor Education in the Americas Project (US/LEAP), Chicago, IL, 2004 (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - Wisconsin Labor History News: Wisconsin Labor History Society, Milwaukee, WI, 1990 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Progress Report: Work in America Institute, Inc., 1988 (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - Southern Cotton Mills and Labor: Workers Library Publishers, 1929 (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - Why We March for Unemployment Insurance!: Workers Library Publishers, 1932 (Box 162, Folder 11)
  - Neponset Review, 1915 (Box 83, Folder 7)